THEME SONG: In the
not-too-distant future way
down in Deep 13, Dr.
Forrester and TV's Frank
were hatching an evil scheme.
They hired a temp by the name
of Mike, just a regular Joe
they didn't like.
Their experiment needed
a good test case,
so they conked him on the noggin
and they shot him into space.
Get me down!
We'll send him cheesy movies
the worst we can find.
He'll have to sit
and watch them all,
and we'll monitor his mind.
Now keep in mind
Mike can't control
where the movies begin or end.
He'll try to keep his sanity,
with the help of his robot
friends.
Robot Roll Call!
Cambot!
Show yourself!
Gypsy!
I'm not ready!
Tom Servo!
Hello there!
Crow!
That's one O.
If you're wondering how he eats
and breathes, and other science
facts, just repeat to
yourself, "it's just a show.
I should really just relax for
Mystery Science Theater 3000!"
-Hey guys, hey,
get a load of this.
It says here there was a
house in Saint Paul, Minnesota
that was knee-deep in garbage.
They had to use the bathtub
as a trash receptacle.
Can you believe that?
-Now that is pathetic.
You know, Benjamin
Franklin had a great quote
about cleanliness.
Actually, I wrote it down.
It's around here somewhere.
-Say, do any of you
notice a weird smell?
-Hah!
He who smelt it, dealt it!
-He who denied it supplied it!
-Oh no, it's not
that kind of smell!
-Oh.
-Yeah, I know.
It's kind of a faint, soggy,
rotting, melting, industrial,
grandma smell.
-Yeah, I smell it too.
-I wonder what it could be.
Hmm.
[All sniffing]
-Huh.
-What is it?
Kind of a Jean Nate
jock strap rotted thing?
-Meat vanilla catcher's
mitt squirrel--
-Horseradish Slim Jim croppy--
-Kind of thing?
Just vaguely?
Eh, maybe not.
-Ooh, uh, Dirty Boy and
Service Master are calling!
-Oh, I got it!
-Ugh.
-Mike!
Yuck!
Icky!
Look at you.
You're living in your own filth.
Eugh.
You don't see us
doing that, do you?
Why-- Why, see how
clean Frank is?
-Thank you, Clay.
And you're very clean also.
And you smell wonderful.
-Well, Frank, as you know,
I bathe myself thoroughly
whenever I get the chance.
-Well, I make the time to scrub
myself six times every day.
-Oh, yeah?
Well, I'm constantly
digging under my nails,
between my toes,
and behind my ears.
-I soak myself for three
hours after every meal.
-I've basically been in
the shower since Tuesday.
-And you stopped.
And the slime and
the dirt just oozes--
-Oh, you're a fine one to talk!
You with your clammy body!
-Clammy?
I'm-- You're clammy!
-You're King Clammy!
-You're clammy!
BOTH YELLING: Clammy!
Clammy!
-Ha ha ha ha!
You know, guys, I think we
the Mads a hearty thanks!
It did get a little out
of hand up here, eh?
-Another load heads
toward the sun.
-Yeah, it's fun to clean.
And you know, look at all the
great stuff we're finding, too.
-Look at that.
-Hey!
Hey, that my mother!
Well, still.
Everything's got to go.
Bye Mom!
-Another load heads
toward the sun.
-Ok.
Let's take a look at
a job well done, eh?
Cambot, give me
rocket number nine.
-Ahh.
Hey, again, thanks for
the gentle hint, guys.
-Whoa!
Whoa!
That thing's still moving!
[Yelling]
-I see a germ!
-I see a disgusting worm on you!
-Anyway, Mike.
First up, "A Day at the Fair."
Then we have "Code
Name: Diamond Head."
Push the button, Frank.
-Forget it!
-Push the button!
-I'm not done washing!
-Oh, I'll get it.
-Oh, you would do that.
[Gargling]
-Ok.
There.
That makes us feel a
whole lot better, huh?
-Yes, and it brightens
the place up.
[Buzzing]
-Oh!
I'll stay.
You guys have a movie to watch.
Go!
-Goody. "A Day at the Fair."
-Ooh.
Hey, I didn't finish
NARRATOR: This is
the fairground,
where the fair is held.
-Any questions so far?
NARRATOR: Every year
about this time, this
becomes a place of
work and excitement.
-And romance, and intrigue!
NARRATOR: They're getting
ready to hold the fair.
-These plucky Kiwanis
stand to make a bundle.
NARRATOR: Here, the
fun of the fair--
-Ooh, my foot foot!
NARRATOR: --is in the making.
-Ooh!
NARRATOR: All the
shows and rides
and make-believe of the midway.
-Ugh, Freddy Krueger.
NARRATOR: Here too,
from far and near,
farm folks are bringing in
the products of the harvest,
the choicest of their animals.
-Their dates.
NARRATOR: The
finest of the things
that are grown on the farms.
-Thank you, thank you.
Couldn't have done it
without old Ed here.
NARRATOR: Here, at
the Olson's farm--
-Pain is everywhere.
NARRATOR: --ready
for the fair too.
-He raises Dead End Kids!
NARRATOR: Into the truck
goes one of the calves
that Johnny Olson has raised.
-Tell us what they've
won, Johnny Olson!
NARRATOR: --boys is taking
his finest calf to the fair.
This is Johnny--
-The mean one.
NARRATOR: --his
bigger brother, Bob.
-They need Rogaine.
NARRATOR: Sister
Anne is going, too.
-Let me out!
NARRATOR: She's
taking her four pigs.
-Hitler's Death Car!
NARRATOR: Mrs. Olson
is ready to start,
but first she must see what Mr.
Olson is taking to the fair.
-Oh, not your gallstones, Henry.
NARRATOR: It's a sample of his
corn, the very finest ears.
-And the small of his
neck is nice, too.
NARRATOR: Everyone ready?
-No.
NARRATOR: It's time to go.
-No one can explain
why Father is 85.
NARRATOR: And now they're off.
-Vroom.
NARRATOR: With their corn,
their pigs, and their calves.
-Whee.
NARRATOR: To have a day of
work and of fun at the fair.
-Pa, slow down, you're doing 15!
-There's no one driving!
It's a phantom truck!
-Whoo!
NARRATOR: Here, in the big
cattle barn on the fairground,
folks are at work early,
tending and grooming.
-Thank god methane rises.
NARRATOR: Bob and Johnny
are there early too.
They're getting their
calves ready for the show.
-Did Donna do this rinse?
NARRATOR: They comb and
brush the calves' coats--
-[grunting]
NARRATOR: --until
they're smooth and sleek.
-It's head's gone, stop rubbing.
NARRATOR: The boys want the
calves to look their best.
-You want bangs this time?
Let's go with bangs, honey.
This will be so nice.
NARRATOR: Over here, Anne
is busy grooming her pig.
-Dad heads for the
caning exhibit.
NARRATOR: She powders them all
over to make them look whiter.
-[SNORTING] (SINGING) A
sprinkle a day keeps odor away.
NARRATOR: See how
spotlessly clean they are.
-Which makes them so attractive.
-Who cares?
They're pigs.
NARRATOR: But now, there's
time to go sight-seeing.
Johnny goes first,
to see the fish.
-(DUMB VOICE) I like fish.
NARRATOR: Say, these bass would
make good fishing, if only
they were in the
creek back home.
-Well see, they were in the
creek, but they've been caught,
and that's why they're here.
NARRATOR: At the
4-H club show, Anne
stops to see the model rooms.
-It's the grandma look.
NARRATOR: These have been
made by the 4-H club girls.
-(GRUNTING VOICE)
Ah, look at that.
NARRATOR: Brother Bob is
interested in the butterfly
collection.
-Too interested.
NARRATOR: Here's a beautiful
case of butterflies and moths.
This is one of the many exhibits
made by the 4-H club boys.
-Later, these moths turn up
in the mouth of Bob's victims.
NARRATOR: Anne and
her mother like
to see the home canning show.
Here are rows of fine canned
fruits and vegetables.
But Anne thinks her mother's
canning is just as nice.
-Pickles pack the stands
for the Pickle Races!
NARRATOR: What's this?
-Evil!
NARRATOR: Homemade cakes.
-Thank you Mrs. Khrushchev.
NARRATOR: The judge is deciding
which one of them is best.
-Eh, this is good enough
NARRATOR: First,
she feels the cake.
-Then she rubs it into her hair.
NARRATOR: Then she tastes it.
-What the hell is this?
Judging cakes ought to be fun.
-But this woman sucks
the joy out of it.
NARRATOR: Here,
in the grain show,
Mr. Olson is watching
while the judge decides
which farmer has the best corn.
-I'll pay ya.
Come on, pick mine.
NARRATOR: The judge feels the
weight and shape of the ears.
-It's all done behind
protective chicken wire.
NARRATOR: Then, he looks at the
evenness of the rows of grain--
-Yes.
NARRATOR: --and the size
and shape of the kernels.
-Oh my, yes.
Yes, nice, oh.
NARRATOR: But surely none of
the corn is quite as fine as Mr.
Olson's.
-Don't tell your mother
we've been here, son.
NARRATOR: It's time for lunch.
-Let's go eat something great.
NARRATOR: Most of the
visitors at the fair
have a quick bite at
one of the lunch stands.
-I'm lost.
Mother!
NARRATOR: And my
foot-long hot dog
looks mighty good to these boys.
-Watch the boy on the left.
His heart's about to explode!
Wait!
NARRATOR: But here at
the 4-H club camp--
-Is good, ya?
NARRATOR: --where many
of the farm boys eat,
they get fried chicken
with all the trimmings.
-What, tinsel?
Little lights?
-This is an actual
4-H feeding frenzy!
NARRATOR: Other fairgoers
like to picnic on the grass,
like this.
-Grazing in the grass is a
gas, baby, can you dig it?
-Next up, freaks of nature!
NARRATOR: Bob still
has lots to see.
This is a jet plane.
-Where's the corn go?
NARRATOR: Wonder what it
would be like to fly it?
-Over Cambodia,
secretly maintaining
plausible deniability.
NARRATOR: Here is a tractor.
It's much like the
one Bob's father has.
-Except this one doesn't have
father's arm stuck in it.
NARRATOR: He knows how
to drive this all right.
-OK, I'm a half a mile to the
interstate and I'm outta here!
NARRATOR: Say,
listen to the band.
It's time for the parade!
-It's the Girl Corps, 100
magnificently trained girls!
-(SINGING IN HIGH VOICE) Here
we are now, entertain us.
I feel stupid, and contagious.
-Admiral Halsey joins the fun.
The family of shame.
Captured pilots are paraded
before the citizens.
-Women are excited by
seeing the word "member."
-(IN HIGH VOICE) Oh, my!
NARRATOR: The parade is put
on by the farmers' clubs
from all over the state.
-Scientists aren't sure
what this represents.
NARRATOR: This float was made
up by one of the 4-H clubs.
-In about two minutes.
NARRATOR: Now at the grandstand,
the races are beginning.
-Get the car, there's
carrots in the car!
-Carrots?
I love carrots.
NARRATOR: And here come the
racers down the track and away.
-A wheel slices into the
crowd, killing three.
-Aiyee!
-Still, nothing measures
up to those bats, huh?
NARRATOR: Here they come,
up the back stretch.
-I gotta go, I gotta
go, I really gotta go.
NARRATOR: And Bob gets
there just in time.
They're into the curve.
-And they're into jazz.
-Come on, you trunk of dog food!
I've got a year's
allowance on ya!
NARRATOR: They're going
into the home stretch.
-Oh, hey guys, wait up.
NARRATOR: And here they
come across the finish.
The race is over.
-And the Oak Ridge
Boys take the stage.
-[Mumbled_singing]
-Dad, I owe Big Lenny 42 large.
NARRATOR: Now it's
time for the calf show.
Bob and Johnny are putting
the finishing touches
on their calves.
-Adding hooker
headers and decals.
NARRATOR: Johnny
polishes up the horns--
-[making_squeaking_noises]
NARRATOR: And father,
of course, stands by.
-Doing nothing.
NARRATOR: Now the
boys take their calves
to the arena, where
the show is beginning.
-First is the evening
gown competition.
-We have some tape of the
cows playing on the beach
earlier this week.
NARRATOR: Into the
big, shadowy arena,
many other boys and girls
are leading their calves.
Here come Bob and Johnny.
-What?
I'm not sweating.
NARRATOR: They take their
places in a long line.
-What losers!
NARRATOR: And the
judge is to choose
which among all these
calves is the best.
-But all the calves
are winners, really.
It's just great that
they got involved!
NARRATOR: Bob and Johnny
hope he'll choose theirs.
-Whoop!
Hey, that's my scar.
NARRATOR: Up here, the
folks are looking on.
-Let's get busy
in the car, honey.
NARRATOR: Now the judge
is coming down the line.
He looks at each calf
closely with a practiced eye,
and quickly sees the best
and the weakest point.
-He is all-knowing and wise.
NARRATOR: Now he orders
the doubtful calves out
of the show.
-The Masked Avenger
cow is eliminated.
-I hate these cattle calls.
NARRATOR: Too bad.
Bob loses out.
-Bob hates himself.
NARRATOR: But what about Johnny?
He's still in line.
And now the judge wants to
see his calf in the open.
-He realizes he had not
known cow until this day.
NARRATOR: He looks at
Johnny's calf very carefully.
-He feels a stirring.
NARRATOR: What's this?
Here's Johnny back in line.
Well, it looks like
he has a winner.
-Men are fools, dear.
Remember that.
NARRATOR: Now the
judge is picking out
the champion of them all.
-I am the greatest!
NARRATOR: It takes careful work
to choose the calf with just
the right size, and build,
and weight, and firmness.
-And overall panache!
NARRATOR: One by one, the
judge ranks the calves
and sends them back to their
proper places in the line.
-Life goes on, dull as before.
NARRATOR: At last,
the choice is made.
-But he won't tell anyone!
It's so frustrating.
NARRATOR: The
judge's work is done.
He has picked the winners.
-Quite a coup, getting
Clarence Darrow to judge.
-And the crowd goes wild.
-(DULLY) Yay.
NARRATOR: Well, the champion's
blue ribbon goes to a girl.
-The cows are furious!
NARRATOR: Johnny
gets a ribbon, too.
-Yeah, thanks.
NARRATOR: His calf is a winner.
-Oh, look at this, I
got a stinkin' ribbon.
NARRATOR: Now the day's work
is over, and it's time for fun.
-So they leave the fair.
NARRATOR: The
gates to the midway
open on 100 ways of having fun.
-Or you can just get hammered.
NARRATOR: There are shows
and games of every kind.
And, best of all, a thrilling
ride on the giant Ferris wheel.
-It's the Man in
the Hat exhibit!
-Musty carnies,
drunk by 10:00 AM!
NARRATOR: Here they go,
quickly into the seat,
with the bar fastened tight
to keep them in safely.
-Goodbye, Susan.
If anything should
happen, I love you.
I love you too, Petey.
NARRATOR: And now
the wheel turns.
Up, up, high in the air.
And this is how it seems to
ride the big Ferris wheel.
-It's this disappointing.
-The director got Artie here!
-(SINGING) Love roller coaster!
-Well, Ferris wheel.
NARRATOR: And now for
a ride on The Whip.
-[Vomiting_sounds]
NARRATOR: This is how it
seems to ride on the swooping,
whirling Whip.
-This is how it seems
to be thrown clear
as the cables snap.
NARRATOR: Too soon,
the rides are over.
-The lawsuits begin.
NARRATOR: And too soon, all
the fun comes to an end.
-[Singing_incomprehensibly]
NARRATOR: But our
friends are very happy.
They've had a wonderful
day at the fair.
-You spent your nickel!
We're done!
-Ah!
Tonight on Generic TV Movie.
[Theme music playing]
-Hey, watch out for my bike!
-Hey, I cracked their code.
I'm pretty sure it's
called "Diamond Head."
-Code Name-- Cubic
Zirconium Head.
-Quinn Martin considered
this is most personal film.
-Mm, father what a waste.
-Is he our action hero?
-I want to see Don Ho!
-Ward, dear, would you see
what little Elvis is up to?
-Ah, a little Maui Wowie
to start things off.
-Hey, that's no priest!
That's Lovejoy!
-Rosie O'Donnell
in "The Gauntlet."
-I want a picture of Lovejoy.
-Susan, you sit next to Lovejoy.
-Martin Short.
-I see my latest exhibit
meets with your approval.
-Apparently Jack Lorde doesn't
even like it here, huh?
-Taking a Greyhound to
Hawaii wasn't a good idea.
-Ah, Mr. Jesus.
You have a nasty
habit of surviving.
-That's mine.
I think that's mine.
-That one?
-Yeah.
-Ah, the gripping
luggage sequence.
I'm not going to tell
you what happens.
I'm just going to say--
someone's luggage gets lost!
-Ah, Mr. Handbag.
Once again, I see that you
are not on the carousel yet.
-They'd better not lose my
Saint Peter's finger bone.
-He looks like he just
got out of gym class.
-That guy's a sinner.
They're all sinners.
CUSTOMS OFFICER (OFFSCREEN):
Anything to declare?
-I declare my genius!
CUSTOMS OFFICER
(OFFSCREEN): Thank you, sir.
-Hey, that guy!
What was he in?
-Yeah!
Uh, um.
-Was that guy in?
-Well, hello.
Nomine Patris.
Heh.
-Anything to declare, sir?
-I'm Lovejoy.
Oops!
-Not unless you wish
to make a donation.
I'm on a fundraising tour
of your lovely island.
-Yeah.
Anything to declare?
-Maybe next time.
Good luck.
-Thank you.
-Kisses!
-Enjoy the cocaine, father!
LOUDSPEAKER: Luggage
for flight 05, Chicago--
-Take over for me, will you?
-You make a weak Lovejoy.
-Dammit, security guard!
This is not your personal war!
-Uh, yeah, Vatican?
I just met one of your priests.
Real nice guy.
Thanks.
-This is for Aunt Mary.
-(OLD LADY VOICE)
What do you want?
I was about to have
my fruit cocktail.
And now I've got to get
off the couch, walk over--
-Hi, I'm Jeanie at DeVry.
-Hey, anybody here
know an Aunt Mary?
-Forbin Project,
how can we help you?
-Go ahead, you're clear to
send message to Aunt Mary.
-Code Two.
Tree may be in Paradise.
-What the hell does that mean?
Over.
-On surveillance.
-Roger.
Message received.
-What is the nature
of the priest?
Over.
-I should call Aunt
Mary more often.
-Sure?
Ah, I'm just waiting
for my sister.
Can I help you?
What are you doing?
-This is a job for Regular Guy!
-What the hell was I in?
I know I know me.
-Hi, Mom.
Can you follow that priest?
Thanks.
-I'm ODing on intrigue!
-Who needs to go
coconuts a little?
-This is no good.
Why are you dropping me here?
Oh, that's right.
I'm a priest!
-They are really exploiting
the island locations.
-Code Name-- Gran Torino.
-This guy screams
Ford administration.
-How many of these crappy
Hawaiian pesos you want there?
-It's American.
-Someone should make
love to this man.
-Well, you only rent holy water.
-I'll just get a bulletin
and tell Mom I went.
-It was just a whim
to follow that guy,
and now I'm going to
get in trouble at work.
-Hello?
I'm no longer at La Brea 772.
-Ha!
Come back to AT&T!
-Where are you friends
and family now?
-Well, we finally got
those horrible paintings
off the ceiling.
You know, the Angelos
were here and they
love that sort of thing.
But there's this wonderful
natural brick underneath.
-Whip this congregation
into shape.
-Lovejoy's a hangin' priest.
-And you're certain
nobody saw you?
-I came in through
the side door.
-This is why I dislike
organized religion.
-Vatican II-- The
Final Reckoning.
-Shame you broke my cover.
Now I won't be able to
give you my blessing.
-Go in peace and live no more.
-The bells of St. Murder!
-Die in my bell.
-Hey, you trying to
give me the high hat?
Ed Asner on ukulele.
-He's got a sandwich.
-That's the smallest pool
table I've ever seen!
-Or the biggest woman.
-Somebody told me I had the
personality of one of these,
so I'm curious.
-It looks like he's got about,
oh, $0.15 in his pocket there!
-Play pool the Pat Boone way.
-Ah, the patented banial waist.
Yes.
No visible panty line.
I can name that crotch in--
-I say the six ball
in the corner there.
-100 says you don't
even come close.
-Make it a deuce, and I'll
shave it any way you want.
-You've got it.
-Brando!
-Hey, Johnny.
Isn't there anything
you won't bet on?
-Yeah, marriage.
No percentage.
-That's the stupidest
bet I've ever seen!
No checks.
-And none of that
Hawaiian wampum buck.
-Oh, great.
Here comes my mom.
-Aloha, folks.
Nothing to see here.
Keep it moving.
Aloha.
All right, we're looking
for a Mr. Quinn Martin.
Quinn?
Martin?
-Yeah, we found your
dog on the highway.
-Johnny Paul?
-Yeah?
-You're under arrest.
-For what?
-A&B aggravated on the
person
of one Harper Conyers Junior.
-Harper Conyers
Junior, the welsher.
-You believe this, Steve?
-Had a frank and open discussion
about his personal finances.
All right?
The charges were
dropped a month ago.
I was told to bring
you in, period.
-Paragraph.
-Eh, all right.
I'm all yours.
Marie, keep the party
going, huh baby?
-She'll look like a game of ring
toss before the night's over!
-Eight ball, corner pocket.
-Hey, you wrecked the game!
-Roy Thinnes is locked
outside for life.
-Mr. Woodman!
-Look Kotter, I
don't like your kids.
-(SINGING) Ah, ah, ah, ah,
stayin' alive, stayin' alive.
-He looks like he belongs
on the Ben Hogan tour.
-Aunt Mary.
I could have found you
without this escort.
-I needed you fast.
Besides, it's good
for your image.
-So is the luau I was having.
-Well, I could have
been pruning roses.
Now, there's a time and
there's a place for fun
and games, Johnny.
-And I was stir frying.
-I guess that's why you
cashiered me out of the Navy
and stuck me into this
assignment in paradise.
-I know my people.
Besides, with three
generations of Annapolis blood
in your veins, I knew you
wouldn't turn me down.
-OK, enough back story.
-Well next time use a
telephone, will you?
-Telephones can be tapped.
This place can't.
-Trouble, huh?
-I need the first team.
Do you know this man?
Sean Donovan
-Lovejoy, huh.
Hey, I can't pay this tab!
-One of the best, until
he went freelance and sold
out his whole
network, 28 agents.
This was in 1973.
A year ago, he was spotted
by a stringer in Manila.
New identity, code name Tree.
-He should branch out.
-Tree?
Here in Honolulu?
-I had a call this morning
from one of men at the airport.
Before I could get
back to him, he
was found hanging from
a rope in a church.
-Was he well hanged?
-Well, the Navy's working
on a new magnetic torpedo
at Kaneohe.
-Project Magnotorp.
-The lab is working
on a 21st century
chemical explosive
out at Makapu'u
Maca-poco-diki-baka.
-The Korean ambassador is
due sometime this week.
They're loading a new Phoenix
missile on the aircraft
carrier, and we've just
opened a new top-secret
telecommunications center for
the entire Pacific intelligence
command.
-It's not top-secret now, jerk.
---one of those reasons
or something else.
-Donovan has used at least
12 different identities.
He's a master.
But he likes ladies
and he likes gambling--
-Pervert.
---in that order.
I want you to find him, find
out why he's here, and stop him.
I'll give you all
the people you want.
-Ah.
Zulu and Tso-Tsing.
That's all I need.
-Oh, and Bernie.
-Are you certain your
gambler cover is clean?
-Stop yelling!
-Well it better be.
Because if you know about Tree,
Tree knows about Diamond Head.
-Aunt Mary, stop yelling!
Shut up, Aunt Mary.
-I give you 20-1 odds
I find him first.
-That Loudon Wainwright.
Ha!
What a-- Hey, do you mind?
I'm reading here.
What's that smell?
Do you have to breathe on me?
-Shut up!
-Jeez.
Oh wait, I want to
read Hugh Sidey.
-All right, that's
it little boy.
Come on, come on.
We are going to dance.
-Hey, hey hey!
Guys, guys!
Come on!
Be nice.
Is it so hard to be nice?
-Yes.
-God.
You know, you guys shouldn't
open these pop cans
if you're not going
to finish them.
Ok?
All right.
Now be nice.
I'll see you.
-Sure, thanks Mike.
Good advice.
Dope.
-If you ask me, Mike would
be a little more interesting
if he weren't so nice.
WOMAN'S VOICE: Oh, is that so?
-Magic voice!
WOMAN'S VOICE:
Seems to me you two
don't appreciate Mike
the way you should.
That's why Cambot, through the
magic of his advanced computer
technology, has put together a
little presentation to give you
a little peek of
what it would be
like to be around someone
who wasn't so nice.
Watch the monitors.
-Ha ha ha.
Look at that, Servo.
I'd like to learn
that magic trick.
-That's fun, huh?
-I suppose you think
you're being a smart aleck,
don't you mister?
Well, you let me
tell you something.
I'll wipe that smile
right off your face.
-I was just--
-"I was just!"
Shut your pie hole.
I know a thing or two
about a thing or two.
I'm not going to take
any lip from you,
I'll tell you that right now.
-But we didn't--
-"We didn't!"
-Ow!
-You shut your pie hole.
-"Ow, ow, don't hit
me, don't hit me."
I'm not the raise any sissies.
I'll tell you that right now.
I know a thing or two
about a thing or two.
You guys got it
easy around here,
I'll tell you that right now.
Look at this.
Who opened this pop?
-Uh--
-Is this pop done?
-No.
Look at that.
Look at that pop.
Is that done?
You finish this pop.
What about you?
Look at this.
Did you put this pop down here?
Look at that.
Is that done?
That's not done.
That's a done pop, OK?
[Both sobbing]
-OK, Cambot, we've seen enough.
-Turn it off, turn it off!
-You guys done with
these magazines?
[Both scream]
-Wow, all right.
Uh, OK if I finish your soda?
Mm.
[Theme music playing]
JOHNNY PAUL (OFFSCREEN):
That's right, Father.
-What?
-Honolulu's the
fastest-growing--
-Who?
-Is it you?
-Are you the nice one?
-What do you mean?
-I liked it better
when the clipper just
flew in once a week.
I remember the day
when there were just
two hotels on Waikiki.
-Yeah.
-Code Name-- Receding.
-Paradise sacrificed
to progress.
Only three people
living in the rectory?
-Yes, it's myself,
Father Wong, and Miss Ho.
-Oh, your ho.
-She's over 70.
She's been my
housekeeper for 16 years.
-She's still hot.
-Any visitors?
Well, apart from the poor
soul who died up there.
-Sanctuary!
-That was terrible.
That was just terrible.
-Sorry, corned beef.
Blugh.
-Oh, yes.
There was a Father Horton,
a Jesuit missionary.
He had to leave just after
he'd been here for an hour.
He had some bad news
from home, he said.
He was a lovely man.
Lovely man.
-Did he have to travel alone?
-No, I did see the two
men who came for him.
They were old
parishioners, he said.
-Asians?
-Just one of them.
Twisted old limey.
-Well, this is a
very nice place.
I could see why families
would want to-- Waa!
-Whoa!
-Ooh, he's got a
Jackie Mason body.
[Singing in hawaiian]
-The music is cool,
but the words!
Man. [WHISTLES]
-[Nonsense_fast_singing]
-This is a song all about
how he hates Jack Ward.
-Well, he's still got it.
-I remember when
we used to go out.
He was such fun.
-Wow, he's got
the hips for this.
-Pick-a-little, talk-a-little,
pick-a-little, talk-a-little,
cheep, cheep, cheep, talk
a lot, pick a little more.
-Everybody!
-When's Dave Dalbano come out?
-Gabby Pahinui has
left the building.
-Hey, Johnny!
Want an autograph?
-No, why?
-I didn't know you could write.
Great job.
-Heavy?
-Heavy-ish.
-Mm, aren't they always?
Come on.
A couple of strangers in
town, back alley types.
One Caucasian, dark and wiry.
The other is Asian, I
think he's Japanese.
You've got to find
him, all right?
-Sure, can do.
-But listen, Zulu.
These guys are heavyweights.
So ask quiet, huh?
-Like a mouse?
-You are a delightful man.
-Like a mouse, all right.
-A large mouse.
-I don't feel fresh, Johnny.
-(SINGING) Loving you.
[Whistles]
-The lovely El
Hawaii condominiums.
-With off-street parking.
-Bellbottoms cleaned daily.
-Boy is this
authentic around here.
Golly.
-Yeah.
-(IN HIGH VOICE) Hmm, let's see.
If I don't eat for a month--
-The world of Susie Wong, CPA.
-(IN HIGH VOICE) Hm, did
I want separate checks?
-Look, she's plucked
her forehead to death.
-(IN HIGH VOICE) Yeah, well
my PhDs worth a hell of a lot.
-Zip.
Zip.
-(IN HIGH VOICE) Oh, my bones
came through my skin again.
Huh.
-Guess who?!
-Don't you ever knock?
-Mm-mm.
Spoils the fun.
-Yeah, fun.
Heh heh heh.
Fun.
-I think the fun
is already spoiled.
-Yep.
I've got to find this man fast.
-There he is!
-He might be working
for the same outfit
that nailed you in Bangkok.
-Don't start.
-You know how rough they play.
-Is this a bar where
nobody knows your name?
-OK, she leaves.
My line is-- Ah.
-So, uh, you guys hiring
any bus help or anything?
Can I get a water
or some crackers?
---to me or how they did it.
-I never got my side of fries.
---my family.
All of them.
-I'm going to sit this
scene out if you don't mind.
-Are they talking
about the same thing?
-Why, Johnny?
Why us?
-Well, we'll always
have something or other.
-Every day, people
get shot down.
-Bo-wing.
-People get tortured
by professionals
who are paid by
so-called patriots.
-Like Marty Ingels.
-It's become fashionable
for presidents to lie,
diplomats to steal,
oil companies
to sponsor revolutions.
-Look, just take
your last paycheck.
I sorry, but you ate
out of the bus tub.
-Some people can
live with the taste.
I can't.
-(SINGING) We didn't
start the fire!
-Maybe I just like to
play with matches, huh?
-There's my smile!
-It looks like it
hurts to do that.
-As long as we don't
burn our fingers.
-We won't.
-Ow!
My fingers!
-Hey, she's wearing ooga horns!
-Well, where do we start?
-Well.
-Well, let's look
at my deductions.
-We don't know what
cover he's using.
It'll be British,
Irish, Australian--
-French, Italian,
poppy seed, hot ranch.
---hundred men that
fit that description.
-This one likes pretty ladies.
-Hmm.
You're getting warmer.
-Likes to gamble.
Your back room.
Roulette.
-How many words?
Sounds like--
-That's for members only,
and well-heeled swingers.
-(SINGING) With an
awful lot of lettuce.
-Tso-Tsing, what I'm
trying to tell you
is that you're not going
to have to look hard.
If this guy is in Hawaii,
he's going to find you.
-Oh, are they in Hawaii?
-Ohhh.
-I'm stuck in this position.
Help!
-Ciao.
-Puppy chow.
I'm so hungry.
-Actual Lovejoy footage.
-Oh, he's been
promoted to Monsignor.
-Mrs. Bates wants her hair back.
-I've had a bitch of a day.
-It's either the
world's worst haircut
or the world's worst wig.
-Vatican t-shirts--
move with you.
-Gaddafi?
He's wearing a leisure uniform!
-Er, where's my picture?
Curtis LeMay.
Yeah, there it is.
There.
-The only South American junta
leader in the American Army.
-Robbie Robertson
on dress-up day.
-Damn, they gave me
clown white by mistake.
-(SINGING) I feel pretty.
-Now some red, red lipstick
to bring out my teeth.
-Oh, no, sir.
Not Othello.
-I don't know why they wanted
me to go undercover as Carol
Channing, but--
-Hey, what happened
to Ian McShane?
-Going as John Waters?
-Now, now he's
going as Rip Taylor.
-I'm a general, it's funny!
Hah!
-Not really a
perfectionist, is he?
-Now who's that guy?
Hoh, it's me, I'm kidding.
-Now I can take
tolls wherever I go.
-Admiral Sid Dithers.
-That's it, get out!
I don't want to talk about
it, sir, just-- just get out!
Go!
Hey look, it's "and Tennille."
-You have brunch here?
-My name is Commander Yarnell.
Would you call Colonel
Millard Butler,
please, and tell
him that we're here?
-Certainly, sir.
-You see, nobody
knows what I'm in!
-Tell Commander Yarnell
I'll be right down.
-I'm dressed right
for the hot tub.
-Would you like this
apple-white shoulders?
There.
-Ohhh, they're stealing
his Blue Blockers.
There.
-Ah ha ha.
Lovejoy versus Lovejoy.
-Pose him picking his nose!
Heh heh.
-Wow.
Whoa, wow!
Hoh hoh.
Got to get some reading glasses.
-There.
I am the very model of
a modern major general.
-Not bad at all if
I do say so myself.
[Snoring]
-Hi, Lovejoy!
-Colonel.
-Hey, it's Lovejoy.
-Welcome to Hawaii.
-Commander.
I always enjoy a vacation
from the Pentagon.
-Professor En-Ping
from the University--
-Peew!
-Professor, I hear you
and your colleagues
have got some surprises
for us up in Makapu'u.
-From what they tell me.
I hope we're the last
men on Earth to see it.
-Hey!
This is a TV movie!
Rip off!
Boo.
-You and your
chaperone will travel
to what is apparently Hawaii!
-Oliver Twist had more Hawaiian
locations than this movie.
-The Kentucky Cycle has
more Hawaii locations.
-Oh, the all-cat food store.
-Oh, I've got to pick up a can
of tampons for my girlfriend.
-Do you have any canned items?
-Across the street, room 205.
Interpol did the rest.
-Just looking, thanks.
-Hikaru Sakai, a street
kamikaze from Tokyo.
He's a professional assassin.
The other guy is Ernest
Graeber, once a contract hit man
for East German intelligence.
-Always a contract hit man
-Calls Tahiti home now.
-Don't smell the bok choi.
-Very bad dudes.
-Where are they now?
-Staying with mom.
-Mama Chongs, eating steaks.
-Well, the three regular team.
-If they show up,
honk twice, huh?
-Yeah, sure.
-Hey, hey!
You've got to pay
for the Sheeva!
-Where in the hell did I park?
-Lot of goofing off in
the undercover business.
-Shout.
Shout.
Let it all out!
-The Eiger Sanction had
more Hawaiian locations
than this movie.
It's the kookiest
surveillance ever!
Hoo-hoo!
-He promised Sid and
Nancy he'd stop by.
-He lives in Hawaii,
but somehow he
still has a furnished
room in St. Paul.
-I just have the urge
to clean this lock.
-Ooh, spidery hands.
-Gollum breaks
into an apartment.
[Muffled]
-Ah, now the payoff.
Ah hah!
-Ergon Cable!
-Just here to drill through
your hardwood floors.
-Wow, that's a big-ass phone.
-This looks like
Daddy-O's apartments.
Except for the big-ass phone.
-Forget it, no way.
There's not a natural
fiber on that man.
-Maybe I'm gonna call
Sydney-- Australia!
-Take one of these now, and
take one after every phone call.
It doesn't do anything, but at
least he knows it's in there.
-This is the movie
poster right there!
Sold millions.
-Isn't that that guy
who was on that show?
What's those shows?
-Sort of a Cannon-y "McMillan
and Wife" type of thing?
-Rope had more Hawaiian
locations than this film!
He's wearing Mary
Tyler Moor's pantsuit.
-Well, he wants the match there.
I'll put it back.
It's kind of weird.
-It's Shirley Hemphill!
-(SINGING) At Bene,
at Beneficial.
[Suspenseful music building]
-Whoooo!
-Oh, what am I going to do?
I'm uncool!
[Imitating suspenseful music]
-I put in a matchstick
and it's foolproof.
Saves on a costly alarm system.
-You smell high karate
something fierce.
-This thing is damp!
-Carmen Miranda's in there.
-Now back to the jaunty
Roy Thinnes theme!
-This is so almost Mitchell.
-It's about 50 pounds
short of Mitchell.
-So.
Any Bilakhia?
-Back to the
exciting tuna store!
-I planted a bug
where they'll be
sure to find it when they do
their move on Tree, I hope.
You stay with them, huh?
-Right.
-And he's good at conveying
incomprehensible plot points.
-Well, it's been nice being
here in downtown Fargo,
but I should be
getting back to Hawaii.
-This is too nice a place for
a deadly game of cat and mouse.
-Aw, people got
to start buttoning
their shirts in this movie!
-Everything seems all right.
-Trust the matchstick.
-One thing is sure.
We had a visitor.
-Let's take this place apart.
-Let's put the ceiling
where the floor is.
-Daddy, let's get a
two-bedroom next time.
It's crowded in here.
-Are these your tap pants?
-I need to call Dad.
Been too long.
-Premature funk music.
-There's always been
a bug in here, right?
-Sakai.
-'S all right.
-There's a rattlesnake
in my phone!
-The new Cadillac
lease program--
a simple up-front
payment of $47,000.
-We can't have Van
Dykes in the Navy!
-It's the slacker Navy.
-See, I've written a lot
of checks to Davanni's.
-Go right in, sir.
-Got the Navy wrapped
around their fingers.
-Yeah, you jerks are
no better than me.
Glad I went through
boot camp for this.
Join the Navy and see the world!
Yeah, more like open gates!
-That's a security guard.
-Oh, sorry.
-Gee, they fenced
in the entire ocean.
-They're making a stop at
the lumber yard, I see!
-We need some
plywood and a thing
to roll the garden hose on.
-OK, do you have brunch?
-Why hello, Captain Stubing!
Merrill.
-Gentlemen.
You've already met
Professor En-Ping.
-Ping!
-Hello, Professor.
-Thank you, Sherman.
Dr. Yamamoto, this
is Colonel Butler.
-Not Lovejoy.
-A pleasure.
-What's with your moustache?
-This isn't the
Pentagon, Colonel,
but I think you'll
find this interesting.
-Oh, I'm sure I will.
Shall we begin?
-The beguine?
Ha!
Little-- never mind.
-For security
reasons, we maintain
our experimental
laboratory below sea level.
-Sure you do.
-Our test began with a rare cone
snail called the cloth of gold.
-Holy cow are they
below sea level.
-On contact, its
microscopic needles
inject alkaloids, which paralyze
the central nervous system.
Instantaneous death.
-And it's so good with kids.
-We extracted the liquid
poison, vaporized it--
-Added some leather.
-The result was astounding.
[Theme music playing]
-Hey Mike!
-Mike!
Mike!
-Hey Mike, Mike.
-Let's play some Litho-Fungo.
-Yeah, come on!
Come on, come on!
-I'd really like
to, guys, but I've
got to finish
alphabetizing my CDs.
I'll see ya.
-Pbb.
Huh.
-Jeez.
I'd like to suggest
that Mike is less than a
fulfilling roommate, but I'm
afraid Magic Voice will--
WOMAN'S VOICE: Thank you, Crow.
I'm not finished with you yet.
Let's see what it would be like
if you lived with, oh, say,
a Crash Test Dummy!
-Brad Roberts?
-[Mumbled_singing]
-That voice!
-It hurts!
-[Mumbled_singing]
-That was close.
-Point taken, Magic Voice.
-All right.
Got the CDs alphabetized.
Who's for Yahtzee?
-Oh yes, oh yes, oh yes!
WOMAN'S VOICE: Movie
sign in three seconds.
Ha ha!
Just kidding.
-Whew!
[Buzzing]
-[Sobbing]
-Don't let go!
-Come on!
-No.
No.
---with unlimited
killing potential.
-Amazing biochemical
breakthrough.
Incredible.
But you must stop these tests.
We outlawed chemical
warfare eight years ago.
How much of this gold
cross have you made?
-Lots!
---with the underwater test.
We've destroyed the rest.
-Normal precautionary
measures, Colonel.
We can't have these experiments
falling into strange hands.
Of course.
-Pssh.
Think I don't know that?
-May I see what
precautions you've taken?
-And top thinking
that I'm Lovejoy.
-We maintain two safety checks.
-And that's about it.
-The gas is locked in
this compression chamber
and kept under pressure.
-Then your class ring
is buffed and polished.
-Oh, that's no good.
That'll ruin a planet.
Ha ha!
-Additionally, the vial
itself is also pressurized.
-I mean, usually
it's pressurized.
-And we pay a high school
kid to keep an eye on it.
-And your research?
-Still got two weeks
before the report's due.
-It's all been
recorded on tapes.
Formulas, chemical
compounds, every step
of the test from
the very beginning,
including the exact
amounts of the mixture.
-Well, when do we see
the underwater test?
-Colonel, surely
you've seen enough.
-Commander, your report
mentioned two tests.
Until I see both
of them, I'm not
authorized to give
a final judgement.
-I hate you.
-Very well, Colonel.
Gentlemen?
-We have to fumigate the
tank, store the toxin.
-We have to completely
redo the upstairs.
-Noon tomorrow?
-Hmm, I was going to
play golf, but no.
-I know they think
I'm Dennis Weaver.
You think I'm Dennis
Weaver too, don't you?
Yes, you do.
You do.
-[Singing "the
girl from ipanema"]
-I hope he owns several
of those shirts.
-Hello there!
-I'd like to make a
person-to-person call
from that one guy
to that other guy.
-Maybe I should
introduce myself.
Maybe he'd like me.
RECEPTIONIST (OFFSCREEN):
Telephone for Colonel Butler.
Call for Colonel Butler.
-Or Lovejoy.
July
-It's hard to organize a
junta in Vacation Land.
-Colonel Butler speaking.
Thank you.
Give him his binky and
put him in his crib.
I don't know.
-There's something else.
-Nobody quite knows
where they've seen me.
-Whoever planted that
bug is an amateur.
-Wrong.
There's an American
in deep cover
here, code name Diamond Head.
And he's good.
He made it too easy for you.
-Meaning what?
-Meaning he expects
you to lead him to me.
You're being followed.
First, use Diamond Head's man
and set up in the diving shop.
Contact our friend.
-Damn, I'm on speaker phone!
-Tell him to prepare the
alternate escape route just
in case.
We go tomorrow as planned.
-What about this Diamond Head?
-He's looking for Tree.
He'll find him.
-How?
That's my job.
Tell Sakai to call me.
I'll do the rest.
-Hold it, turn.
Beautiful!
Perfect!
-Tonight!
One of these three
contestants will find out
where they've seen this guy!
-Tom Jones.
-Ah!
Look at that shirt!
-Move it, Normal Lear.
-Nickle!
-Butt-grabbing slacks.
-When you're proud of
your crack and it shows.
-Speed, starring Keanu Reeves.
-The FBI's going to
pay us all to surf?
-Oh, I better get to the
Banana Splits auditions.
-Jeanie?
-Ugh, he would have
to have trifocals.
-The hair is built into the hat!
[Phone rings]
-Aw, it's probably Sherry.
She probably wants to talk
about the break up again.
-What can I doodly-do you for?
-I'll come up.
-Yes.
-Jeez, he needs some psst.
You know.
-Now where's that
skort outfit I packed?
-Wow!
Ooh-wa!
-You know, I tell you, I
get no respect, no respect.
-Oh, everybody wants
a piece of Lovejoy.
-Graeber said you wanted me.
-In the worst way.
There's a disco
called The Dragon
Lady, moored in Honolulu Harbor.
Be outside on the upper
deck at 2200 hours.
-Problems?
-I'll be posing
as that gentlemen.
-You?
-Basil Philips.
Very British, very obvious.
-Very fey.
-Oh, Sakai.
Take a good look.
I'd hate there to be a case
of mistaken identification.
-That could be fatal.
-We're taking a midnight stroll.
-To Georgia.
-If my instincts
are correct, I'll
be having company--
unwelcome company.
-I understand.
Oh, and Sakai?
-Turn down the bed, will you?
-No marks.
-No hits, no arrows.
-Nothing for the authorities.
-Sakai, if you walk
out that door--
-He's very raccoon-y.
-A good thing he uses
smudge-proof eyeliner.
-Ed Shaughnessy, Hawaiian-style.
-I'll salute to careful shaving.
-I don't know what it is or
how it's done, but I like it!
-San Diego chicken?
Oh.
-Hi.
Here for the Daniel
Inouye fund raiser.
-He's going to have a Montclaire
moment any minute now.
Sir?
Vodka with one ice cube only.
-You're in luck, buddy.
We have one.
-Dear bartender.
I like you.
Do you like me?
Check one.
-Ooh.
-She's saran-wrapped.
-Would you give
this to Tso-Tsing.
-Sure, Mr. Lovejoy!
-Give everyone an
ice cube, on me!
-It's All-Annoying
Music Night down here.
-I hope someone else
is hearing that.
-Stomp, ladies and gentlemen!
Stomp.
-Pshaw.
I could have done that.
-Mr. Phillips?
You asked to see me.
-Not wearing that I didn't.
-Your reputation
doesn't do you justice.
What's Archer pleasure?
-My pleasures are personal.
I never mix them with business.
-Duty and brains in the
same lovely package.
You know, your back room's
almost as famous as you are.
They say luck's a lady.
-Then she should be courted.
-Whoa!
Got a live one here.
Jackie?
-(ANNOYED) What?
There, feel better?
Be sure to come back.
I'm freezing you a
special ice cube!
-Yeah.
Uh, Northstar Ice?
Yeah, I need another ice cube.
Better make it four.
-Tso-Tsing wants you, pronto.
Go
-Ah, go fish.
-The house shows 10.
-Play these.
-Whoa, whoa! [CLEARING THROAT]
-You seem to do well here.
-How much is a four
worth, you know?
-I give my customers what
they want-- the exotic Orient
and no overcharge.
-Anything else?
Information, for example?
-Information is like sex.
You can sell it 50 times
and you still own it.
-Heh, sex.
-An exchange, then.
You for Diamond Head.
-I don't understand.
Mm, good ice cube.
-Five years ago, an American
intelligence agent in Bangkok
lost her cover.
Her family was
liquidated and she
was subject to the
usual brainwashing.
However, her people got her out
and they relocated her here,
in Hawaii-- naturally,
under an assumed identity.
-Is this your dessert menu?
-Tso-Tsing.
-Birthday prayer for
a special friend.
Hmm.
-Kate Jackson!
Ooh, the smart one.
-You have a saying--
all Asians look alike.
-That is so racist!
I-- oh.
Well, I wouldn't
bet my life on that.
-Woo-hoo!
I mean--
-There's a contract
out on this girl,
and there are certain
types here in Honolulu
who would enjoy collecting you.
-That's a weird
hat she's got on.
-Who is Diamond Head?
-You have made a mistake.
I do not know Su-La
or Diamond Head.
-He's got his own airbag.
-Racko!
-Pay 20.
-Tso-Tsing.
Anyone ever tell you
this is against the law?
-[COUGHING] Diamond Head!
[SNEEZING] Diamond Head!
-Uh, it seems I win.
-We are playing
for match stakes.
-Oh, blue tip.
Strike anywhere.
-Oh, congratulations.
-Basil Phillips.
-Johnny Paul.
-Friends call me Diamond Head.
-I should warn you-- Johnny
does this for a living.
-Oh, that pay good?
-What, you want
to chase him away?
-In retrospect, the luggage
seems really fascinating.
-Oh, yeah.
-You look like a gambling
man, Mr. Phillips.
-Well, I, uh-- I take risks.
-I'm in this movie, aren't I?
-But only when I know the
odds and the adversary.
-You make a game of chance
sound like a battlefield.
-Oh, Lovejoy!
-When the stakes are high,
that's exactly what it is.
-The Gospel according
to Napoleon.
-Spoken like a true fop.
-Spoken like a military man.
-I'm lost.
-Is this an action sequence?
-Actually, I'm into
the money game.
You know, real
estate investments,
that kind of thing.
-[Blabbering_incoherently]
-Trying to get a
conversation going.
-But only when I know the odds.
-The house shows a queen.
-Stand.
-Play these.
-Blackjack.
The house wins.
-Correction.
You win.
-(SINGING) Savoir-Faire
is everywhere!
-It's been a, uh, pleasure Mr.--
-Paul.
-Diamond Hea-- uh, Paul.
-Mr. Paul.
-Do try the ice cubes.
If I, uh, hear of
any good investments,
I'll be sure to look you up.
-You do that.
-Is it just me, or
did nothing happen?
-That's one rotten poker player!
-He knows who I am.
And he knows who you are.
-And he knows who he is.
-Get Zulu here fast.
And you stay here,
wait for my call.
-She looks like Jiminy Cricket.
-Sir?
Sir, we're setting up in here.
Sir, could you--
-Oh man, I want
those bellbottoms.
-Action Ken Doll is there!
-Take a picture,
it lasts longer.
-You know, when this originally
aired, at this point everyone
had turned to Carter Country.
-Right, Zulu.
You had better come
over as fast as you can.
-Jenny Craig, put me in reverse!
-[Singing_jazzy_theme]
-Asthmatic hit man.
-We need a table busked, Phil!
-Johnny!
-Fajita!
-Maybe I overreacted!
-Johnny!
-What'd you do that for?
-Like a bird, like a
plane, like an idiot.
-Well.
-Hmm.
-Huh.
-One more minute and he gets his
advanced beginner certificate.
-Come on, you guys
gotta see this.
-Just a little accident.
Everything's under control.
-Mai Tais on the house.
Come on.
-Aw.
Help!
I can't swim.
-[Dolphin_noises]
-Johnny, are you all right?
-Fortunately, polyester
washes up so nicely.
-I told you to stay put.
-Oh, it's my fault.
Tree used my to get to you.
-What are you talking about is?
His man was waiting
up there long before.
It's Tree.
He's been ahead of us
every step of the way.
-What happened?
-Cyanic acid pack from up there.
-Uh-huh.
Got drunk and fell over, huh?
-You're lucky.
-It was the one called Sakai.
What about Graeber?
-I lost him.
He made a phone call at
Waikiki, then evaporated.
-It's Tree again.
You've got to find those two.
They've got to have
a backup somewhere.
-You OK?
-No, I'm not.
But will you get moving?
-I'll bring you their
heads on a plate.
-What about me?
-You bring the sauce.
-You're out of it.
They broke your cover.
You've got to go home, lock
your door, and stay their.
Don't let anyone except me.
-How about you?
-They think I'm dead!
I've got an edge.
-Johnny, please?
-Yeah, I know.
Be careful.
-Actually no.
-[Making_shoe_squishing_noises]
-He kind of looks
like Squiggy now.
-Code name-- Diamond Head Cold!
-[Sneezes]
-Captain!
I have an Aunt Mary Code Seven!
Line two.
It's on scramble.
-(HIGH VOICE) I'm not here!
-Johnny?
-Tree broke my cover.
-How?
-He knows who Tso-Tsing is.
He went for the
phone tap number,
took a big risk in
showing themselves.
He's ready to move.
-All right, I'll tighten up
security all over the island.
-Use the name Basil Phillips,
British I don't think
you'll turn anything up--
-Looks like Simon LeBon.
-Tomorrow.
Same time, same place.
-You.
[Theme music playing]
-Sure.
What with all the poi.
-Code name Bobby Goldsboro here.
-(SINGING) Undercover
Asian, midnight fantasy.
-Augh!
Danny!
-Now, her whole family
gathered around the TV
to watch her on this show.
That was it.
-Ted Turner in "Frenzy."
-Go get help!
-I'm sorry, sir, I'll have
to check your pass again.
-I'm betting they filmed
this scene the same day
as the other scene.
Brilliant!
-They're doppelgangers.
Doppelcoppers.
-Thank you, Colonel.
-Hi, Mr. McCloud.
-Could I stand on that side
of the door for a while?
-Oh, we're so far down
we have the bends.
-Sorry we're running
a little late.
-Please push it, doctor.
The Army kids run
a tight schedule.
May I use your phone?
-Certainly.
Decompression
temperatures, doctor.
Do you have a readout
from the test yesterday?
Yes.
-Colonel, is that a local call?
-The barometric components
varied dramatically
from previous tests.
-Dialing.
-The expansion of the
biochemical reaction
was greater than
we had expected.
-Boy, I sure get
a lot of messages!
-Certainly the
compression factor
wend beyond our calculations.
-Yes honey, I'll
be here a while.
---contain the unexpected
aberrations of compression
and heat--
-Basically pretty
popular, you know.
-But I'm afraid some of
our electronic recording
instruments were not
adequately programmed.
-The Navy keeps ships in
commission a long time,
doesn't it?
-Wow.
-And those of you who would
like to be keelhauled,
go to the right.
Those of you to be
pinswiggled, please
make your way to the left.
---was built by
the Scots in 1878.
It was one of the largest
four-masted square riggers
ever constructed.
She later sailed
from San Francisco
and was converted
to an oil tanker.
And then a long life
freighting oil to Hawaii.
-(IN HIGH VOICE)
But enough about me.
-I am now the sole,
surviving example
of a sailing oil tankers.
-Roy Thinnes-- a cop who
doesn't stay in line!
-Ah, the curio shop.
-Hello, Moneypenny.
-You were right
about Basil Phillips.
He died 40 years ago in infancy.
All Tree did was phony up a
passport, so it's a dead-end.
Anything on Tree's men?
-Not yet.
-Well, we're
running out of time.
-Excuse me, my
underwear is buzzing me.
-Macintosh.
Control.
The body of Colonel
Butler was just
found, apparent
accidental drowning.
Since he was cleared top-secret,
I thought you'd want to know.
-Message received.
Thank you.
And the tourists all
know who you are.
-Butler was a top
ordinance expert.
Pentagon.
Arrived here two days ago.
-What was he doing here?
-Makapu'u Point.
-Makapu pakapu.
-That's it.
-Tree was taking butler's place.
He's after the
chemical explosives.
-This is Aunt Mary.
Patch me through to Yarnell.
-And Shields!
-Sorry, sir.
The line seems to be dead.
We're too late at the lab.
Tree has to have a
backup someplace.
Now find it, Johnny.
-You got it.
-This is Aunt Mary.
I'm ordering full alert.
Repeat-- full alert!
-I want you to go all-out.
Use the station wagon!
-Now let's see.
Sharon Wilkerson,
Debbie Johnson.
Ok.
Go right in, ladies.
-Yeah.
Officer open the gate.
Officer shut the gate.
-GW Bailey.
-All right!
We snuck into the drive-in
with four people in the trunk!
-Woo!
-It's a station wagon.
-Robert DeNiro is clinging
to the bottom of the car.
-All right, gentlemen.
We have filled the
tank with salt water
and pressurized it to
simulate a depth of 40 feet.
Now, if you will
observe, the gold cross
is in the center of the tank.
-Dullsville.
SCIENTIST (OFFSCREEN):
We will be
ready for ignition in
approximately 60 seconds.
-It'll be the longest
60 seconds of your life.
-I cannot program this thing.
It's always 12:00.
SCIENTIST (OFFSCREEN):
This time, it
will ignite on
electrical impulse.
Combustion will be--
-Lip gloss here.
SCIENTIST (OFFSCREEN):
-combination
of the impulse and the
water pressure itself.
-Open channel D, please.
SCIENTIST (OFFSCREEN): -the
heat factor will be minimized.
But expansion due to combustion
-He-- here's a pen.
Who needs a pen?
SCIENTIST (OFFSCREEN): We'll
be really in just a moment.
-Is that poisoned gas
part of the presentation?
-Ooh, good thing he didn't leave
that pen in his pocket open.
-Yeah.
El Markos are like
that-- stinky.
-Well, apparently the Colonel
has his own little agenda
today.
-Here, fall by me, Brad.
-Get help!
-There.
I finally have the dryer
to myself, thank you.
-Just put it on light
fluff for a while.
-(IMITATING DRAMATIC
PIANO RIFF) Bee
bee boo bee doo bee doo doop.
-Boy, it's tough when Barnaby
Jones out-actions you.
Dee doo doo dee doo doo.
-He's checking
his tire pressure.
-Boop bee dee bee
doo doo doop doop.
-An elaborate plan to soften
the military's clothes!
-Yeah, like I mean this.
-At ease.
Hah! 'Cuz they're dead.
-I'm leaving early because
I have things to do.
Don't check down there.
-Well, they managed
to pull that off
without a moment's suspense.
-Oh, even though
it's a caper, there's
still time for a
scenic overlook.
-Oh, that's smart.
They're carpooling
for the heist.
-Robert Goulet, getaway driver.
-Driving Mrs. Lovejoy.
-All right, switch it to
wolof banana will you?
Oh, we can't.
-Now back to "Code Name: Diamond
Head," starring that one guy.
-Oh, this looks
like a good place
to put up the roadside poison
gas stand, don't you think?
-You said you had a cabin.
This is just property!
-That's not a keg, you idiots.
-That was tight Too tight.
-Close doesn't count.
-Wrong.
And Sakai, you were
clumsy last night.
Diamond Head is still alive.
-Look, I saw him fall!
-You missed.
How else could they
be so close behind?
We're only minutes ahead.
-We are still clear.
-Not until we're
off this island.
-You'll let the air out!
And now, they'll have every
artery blocked out of here.
We're in a trap and
it's closing in.
Did you make contact?
-Rendez-vous is
set for 1600 hours.
-Well that's it.
Go to the shop and
get everything ready.
-Hey, hey hey!
No, no!
-Whoa!
Whoa!
-I'll take care of that.
-Sorry, I'm just mad.
Way to guard the
government, jerk.
-But all their
papers were in order.
-Oh, I guess that
makes you a good guard!
-Ah, yes, that's right, Captain.
Butler's gone.
He left with two men
in an official sedan.
-How long were you out?
-5, maybe 10 minutes.
-But all their
papers were in order!
-That formula is lethal.
-Now get out an alert.
HPD, civil authorities,
and the state police.
I want APB on three civilians--
-Oh boy.
---two Caucasians--
-That's it.
---one Asiatic, and--
-Grubner?
---give them the
description of Butler.
-Butler's?
-The real Butler is dead.
The man who stole that
formula is a double agent.
-Who's Butler?
-Now get on it, fast.
Now, let's see if anyone wants
to go to lunch around here.
Lunch?
-I want the Navy, Air Force,
and the Coast Guard commanders
right away.
-Yes sir.
-And put the Campfire
Girls on standby.
[All imitating
suspenseful music]
-Mr. Lord?
Mr. Fat?
Yoo-hoo.
-Great floors!
-Hey, I'm Jack Rod's
palatial estate in Maui!
-He's got hammer toes.
Hammer toes!
[All humming mc hammer -
"you can't touch this"]
-Aw, come on.
We paid to see the whole guy.
-Ah!
He's gonna put
ice down her back!
-Hmm hmm hmm.
I think this week I'll
have something to eat.
-My compliments.
-Thank you!
Wha-- hey!
-Sunlight flatters you
as much as candlelight.
Inside.
-But we still have
to hear them go
[imitating suspenseful music]
-What do you want?
-Inside.
-OK, fellas.
I made some snacks for you.
Enjoy!
-Hey, thanks, Mike.
That's great!
-Want mine?
-Pssh, yeah, like
I'm going to eat it.
-I'd like to suggest that
Mike isn't a very good cook,
but I'm afraid
that Magic Voice--
MAGIC VOICE: That's
right, you integrates.
How would you like to live
with the Frugal Gourmet?
-Hello my friends, and welcome.
Today we are making
Indian saffron soup.
And if you've never had it,
it's absolutely wonderful.
Let's get started.
I was just throwing in
a few more ingredients.
What you need and what
is essential to this dish
is a fresh robot neck.
And look at this thing.
Look.
Isn't that wonderful?
See how it glistens?
-It does.
-This is wonderful.
You know, don't write
in, for heaven's sake.
You know, robots
are not extinct.
They know that in
India, and they
have big, wonderful
meals using fresh robots.
So let's get started.
Now we need to add a
little fresh ground pepper.
-Whoa, whoa, whoa!
-And look at this wonderful
pepper mill that I've got here.
There's a story behind it.
I went over the hills
into Soviet Georgia
and I got it from a little
old woman with a club foot.
We talked and--
-Hello, Mr. Smith!
Can I have your autograph?
-Shut your pie hole!
I'm trying to do a show
here for heaven's sake.
Anyway, I know a thing or
two about a thing or two.
And I know that our time is
done for today, so that's it.
I bid you peace.
-That's horrible.
-It's so horrible.
It was terrible.
I couldn't--
-ok.
How are the snacks, mi amigos?
Oh, Mike, you old fruit!
They're better than
any cloying old Seattle
windbag could ever make.
-Aw, than-- You didn't
have to say that.
-It's true though!
[Interposing voices]
-We're doing some sunset diving,
and I want you to act the part.
-I got the part, I got the part!
-You know, I should
really work on that case,
but I can't remember what it is.
-Johnny!
Hey!
-Fill her up, matey.
-Zulu told me to find you.
He told me to give
you an address.
-Where?
-Well, he said it'd be worth 50.
--Muldoon, where?
-The diving shop on
Barrington Air Street.
Hey Johnny, what about my 50?
-I'm Richard Harris!
-I wonder if they have
anything scuba-y around there.
-Hmm.
-Underwater-ish.
-She's driving, so
technically she's
an accessory to
her own kidnapping.
-Nice Terry Top.
-Whoa, big Johnson.
-That's Mercury.
-Well, big Mercury then.
-Remember, just ask for minnows.
-One last detail.
Outside.
So
-Watch her.
-Sure.
I'll watch her, no problem.
Watching away.
Gawking OK?
Whoa, can do.
-Hey, you're that guy.
-Cheese!
-Her pants are hurting me.
-If those pants were any
tighter, they'd be behind her.
Hmm.
-Ah, urinal cakes.
My favorite
-We're on the
brink of two people
actually interacting for the
first time in this movie.
-Now I smear the
cheese on the counter.
-So they're biting on
leeches today, or what?
Or not?
-I want this cleaned, and
I'll pick it up Tuesday.
-Who I found just before
we left this morning.
He was playing peeping tom.
-He's probably one of
Diamond Head's members.
Means he can't be far behind.
-You still here?
-Take the truck to
Makaha and burn it,
along with the Hawaiian.
Then catch a commercial
flight to Hilo,
and I'll contact you there.
Too bad we haven't got an
apple to put in his mouth.
-Well, I'll stop by
the farmer's market--
-Never mind.
-We just ran out of time.
Let's go.
-But I like being
a hostage here!
-Ah ha, see, it's a clue that
she's somewhere on the island.
-Ahh.
Whoa.
Lovejoy's packed
tight in denim casing.
-Skin on Lovejoy.
That nitrous is for
Grandpa, and I've
got the vegetable
powder for Grandma.
[Car tears out noisily]
-Well.
-Filmed on Minnehaha
Avenue in Minneapolis.
-Only the interiors
were shot in Hawaii.
-Got to get an outboard
motor, but fast!
-Oh, funny.
That store certainly
invites the customers in.
-I wonder if she
left her ring in here
with some wax and
a map or something.
-He's there for
his nursing shift.
-'Scuse me?
Need a dozen shiners?
-Let's see.
She usually leaves a ring,
wax and map thing out
here on a dock someplace.
-You know, there was a time
when Roy Thinnes's agent
returned his calls?
-Begrudgingly, but
he did return them.
-I haggled with this guy.
-[Imitating_suspenseful_music]
-(WITH INDIAN ACCENT) Tonight,
on a very special Ravi Shankar,
pi.
-He's gonna kill a guy
who's detailing his van?
-I'm OK with that.
-Wise guy, hold it.
Hands on top of the head.
Fast.
Move it.
-Aiiyah!
-He had all afternoon to plan
this move but he screwed it up.
-The good guys in this
movie aren't very good.
-Mm-mm.
-'Scuse me.
'Scuse me.
-Just went for some lumber
and get your face kicked in.
-The scattered crates really
add a lot to the ambiance.
-You know, you hardly
ever see this sort
of thing on TV movies.
-Eh, book yourself, Dano.
I'm outta here.
-Now to get to the sag wagon.
-Oh, for-- You are the worst
assistant I've ever had!
-How was your date with Madonna?
I'm kidding.
That must hurt.
-What happened?
-I forgot to duck.
-There were at least 20 of
them and they jumped me!
-You just missed--
a million or two.
No more.
-I'm really a singer.
That's why I'm
tied up like this.
-Let's tie this guy up.
Let HPD do the rest.
Huh?
-I like to use barbed wire.
-Yeah, have your fun.
I'll go capture the terrorists.
-Hey!
My friend has a
ring just like that.
She wants to break up with me.
-Hey, hey hey, that's
the director's Coke.
I'll just call her
and find out what
the whole ring-wax thing means.
-Hello?
Steve?
Roy Thinnes.
Close off the whole island.
Aunt Mary, Code Seven, Urgent.
-Hello dear.
-Johnny?
Tree's headed for
Tso-Tsing's trimaran.
It's The Dragon Lady.
It's moored in Honolulu Harbor.
-A sailboat?
-Sounds fun!
-He must have friends
waiting for him at sea.
-Mac, he's got Tso-Tsing.
-He's got that formula and
we've got to recover it.
-Mac, I want a shot at him!
-Tso-Tsing knows the rules.
-No friends in the house.
-And so do you.
I want to stop that
boat at any cost.
-You owe me.
-Don't you sass your Aunt Mary!
-You've got 30 minutes.
Then I pull the trigger.
-We've got 30 minutes.
-Duh duh duh da da!
Da-- Oh.
-Jeez, they should
take the boat.
Boy, you know, I
remember when this aired.
An entire nation was riveted.
Everyone was talking about it.
-Hey, switch on Name of
the Game now, will ya?
Oh, I forgot, it's
the wrong decade.
-Hmm?
-She was going to name
her boat "The Stereotype,"
but she decided
on "Dragon Lady."
Tonight's episode--
"No Soup With Buffet!"
-It's a pity we
haven't met before.
Espionage is such
a small community.
It's quite like a
little family, really.
-In that we all drink
and hurt each other.
-What's in the bottle?
-Ah.
To some, a whirlwind.
To me, the only reality--
$500,000 in a Swiss bank
account.
-I meant the red bottle.
-Oh, that's Tia Maria.
-Oh.
-Is this Hawaii or Seattle?
-Avast ye-- Oh, forget it.
-How many people died for
your Swiss bank account?
-A lot.
We don't have exact figures yet.
-Cost of running business?
That's a price no one can pay.
Or has the right to.
-Right?
You'll be waving the flag next
and George, Queen and country.
There's no such thing, girl.
The world is run
by politicians--
-Oh, boy.
---demand respectability
without virtue--
[snoring sounds]
---pleasure without payment.
-You without me, sir?
-And blind men to bury
their honorable dead.
I just balance the
scales a little.
-Acting!
-My way.
-Even in Hell, you will
balance the scales.
Right, Mr. Barnaby?
-I know you are, but what am I?
-Just steer.
-I'm sorry, that
was uncalled for.
-Oh no, Sam Elliott!
-(SINGING) Please allow
me to introduce myself.
[Theme music]
-Herbie!
What are you doing?
-Burns and Schreiber
to the rescue!
-Hah, another member
of his crack team.
-Hey, TV's Frank
named that boat!
-He's got a figure
like Marcia Brady!
-Hey, you should
never run on a dock!
-Hey, where's my 50 bucks?
-Don't worry about
it, you'll get it!
Come on, start her up.
-Where are we going?
-Tso-Tsing's trimaran.
It should be on the
outside, Mamala Bay.
-What's in it for me?
-You'll get another 50 bucks!
Now start it up!
-Our hero gets
rattled very easily.
-There's dead involved now.
The intrigue thickens.
-I can't look away.
-That's right.
A trimaran called
The Dragon Lady.
She was probably outside
the Kewalo Basin right now.
-Are we going to overtake?
-Order him into the wind.
If he opens fire, respond.
Stop that boat, no matter what!
-Yes sir.
-[GASPS] Jim Henson!
-On deck.
Standby to get underway.
Take in all lines.
Let's go.
Priority one.
-The Coast Guard-- for men
too chicken to join the Navy!
-Hey!
God.
Like I'm going to get
beat up by a sailor.
-Stay on this course.
Won't be long.
-She's been
surreptitiously spreading
jewelry behind the boat.
-Derek Jarman's "Blue" had
more action than this movie.
-What's this all about, Johnny?
-Where's your flare gun?
-Here, where I always keep it.
What do you want it for?
-What's the range?
The flare'll burst at 100 yards.
-How we gonna warn Tso-Tsing?
-Fly the cocktail flag.
Nobody ever flies
that going out.
-I wonder where there's
a saloon in sight?
[Cheering and laughing]
-All right.
-I hear the club's
gotten really exclusive.
-Stand by for mild
interest on the high seas!
-Ian McShane in "Lint."
-I think we've got company.
-Oh, no.
Mother!
-Who is it?
And I want to know the truth.
-Hong Kong no good.
He runs a charter.
-Gee, your top smells terrific.
-Aw, they're still
tied to the dock.
-Let's see.
Let's see, what else?
Did I give my corrupt
politician spiel yet?
-I think Kennedy died.
-This is like the end of "The
Firm," except it's coherent.
-Really hair legs
for a-- oh, wow.
-I'll stay aft.
-They only get one pass, man.
-Hey, I've let you down yet.
-There's a lot of
money here, Mitchell!
[Goofy chuckling]
-Yes, I'm that guy!
Yup.
-Wow.
The sail is polyester, too.
-Rat patrol!
That's what you were on.
-Watch it, Johnny!
-Watch the shirt jack!
-Johnny!
-One excuse, Tree!
Come on!
-My mom said I couldn't?
Dog ate my homework?
-So he's basically
saying, make my day?
-Yeah.
-That was number
one for lost causes.
-This is such a
satisfying conclusion.
-This was certainly
worth waiting for, huh?
-Yeah.
-Pity we don't have an
apple to put in his mouth!
Hoh.
I had that coming.
-You OK?
-I am now.
-Let's do some nitrous!
-That's the stuff.
-Bad news, fellas!
[Sirens]
-Here comes trouble!
-Either somebody
bursted the law,
or World War III's just started!
-It's all right, Hong Kong.
You just won yourself
a kewpie doll.
-So the whole point of the
capers was novelty items?
-I am so glad they got together.
-Let's switch it over
to Hec Ramsey now.
-Oh, anything.
-Epilogue.
OK, let me guess.
The last words in this film are
going to be "ah ha ha ha ha."
-Aw, baby.
Tu etais incroybable.
That's French.
It means you were incredible.
-[Making_loud_squeaking_noise]
-You never cease to amaze me.
-Chevy Chase?
-I didn't know you could cook.
-I didn't know you could eat.
-I'm a maze of hidden talents.
-Yeah, very well hidden.
-What about my reward, huh?
-I do have some
rare Maori carvings.
-Marijuana carpets?
-(WITH FRENCH ACCENT) I'm
sorry I'm so fat for you.
[Phone ringing]
-[MAKING_GULPING_NOISES]
I have your gum.
-Hello?
-Yeah, this is Quinn Martin.
We're not going to series.
-Yes.
Just a minute.
-Quinn.
-You.
And he didn't give his name.
-I think it's your mother.
-Johnny?
-I can see you.
-I thought you'd like
to know the gold cross
formant has been destroyed.
-Click.
[Imitating dial tone]
-And the British have passed
extradition on Donovan.
Yeah!
Maybe in about, oh, 200 years!
-Well fine.
It's over then, right?
-Oh, this job, yes!
But there is something else.
-Not tonight?
-I'm worried about security
for the Korean ambassador.
-Ohh!
-I'd like you to look into it.
-Well who isn't?
-So tomorrow, same
time, same place.
-Aww, it's so--
It's almost poignant
how they're trying
to set up the series!
-Aww.
No more of that nonsense.
-About the Maori carvings?
-Oh yes, I want to see them.
-(IN HIGH VOICE) They're
in my halter dress.
-I know I'm going to
be very impressed.
[Knocking on door]
-Code Name-- Interruptus!
-Let's go.
ZULU (OFFSCREEN): Hey, Johnny!
-Hello there!
-I can't get this
guy off my back!
-I jus-- Oh.
'Scuse me, ma'am.
Johnny!
You owe me 100 bucks!
-Oh, that's right.
-That guy.
-Yeah.
-He's asked for a party, love.
Come on!
-Oh!
They're throwing the cast party.
Ha.
-Huh.
They rounded up every Jimmy
Buffet fan on the island.
-Oh, not Burl Ives!
-I wouldn't be able to make love
in the same room as Burl Ives.
Mrs. Burl Ives can't make love
-Whoa!
Ooh.
[Laughing]
-Stay tuned for your local
news, next on the Superstation.
-Like there was any talent.
Talent supervisor?
There was none.
-Teets!
Teets!
-Hey, hey!
-It said it, right there.
-Hey, this was filmed in Hawaii.
-Where?
-It said it.
-No.
-Yes!
-Uh-uh.
-Western Airlines,
now out of business.
-That's Hawaii in
the background.
-Ford Motor, now
out of business.
-(ALL SINGING) Ohhhh, a waka
waka waka waka waka waka woo.
Aaand a waka waka waka waka woo.
Ohhhh, a waka waka waka
waka waka waka woo.
Aaand a waka waka waka waka woo!
Woo-hoo!
-Ain't this the life?
Oh, ever since I adopted the
authentic Hawaiian lifestyle,
I feel like a changed man!
-You look like a changed man!
-Well, that is an
attractive skirt.
-Darn right!
-Uh, don't you have some kind
of a top to go with it, though?
-Bah, tops are for tourists.
This look is the real deal!
-If you say so.
-Wait, Mike, Mike!
-Yeah?
-How would you like a
nice Hawaiian punch?
Yeah, that sounds refreshing.
I think I will have one.
Thanks, Crow.
-You want one?
-Yeah.
-You really want a
nice, Hawaiian punch?
-Yes, I do.
-Say, "sure."
-Ok.
Sure!
-Remember, you asked for it!
One Hawaiian punch coming up!
There you go.
-Great.
-Hope you like it.
-Yeah.
Great.
Thanks a lot.
-Ok.
Uh, I probably should read
a letter here, though.
-Wait!
Don't read that letter yet.
Let me interpret the letter in
the authentic Hawaiian fashion
using the expressive
native dance, the hula.
You see, in the hula, every
movement, every bodily nuance,
tells a story.
Here, let me see that
letter for a second.
[Mumbling] Ok.
Here we go.
[SINGING VERY FAST] Whoo!
What do you think, huh?
-That was interesting.
-Thank you.
-Not at all insulting, either.
-Huh?
-No, not at all.
Why don't I read
the letter, though,
for you not acquainted with the
authentic Hawaiian lifestyle?
Put that up on
still store, Cambot.
Thanks a lot.
Uh, this says, "Dear
Mike, Crow, Tom, Gypsy,
and the rest of the crew at
the Satellite of Love, Hi!
Thanks for reading my first
letter on the air on Saturday,
February 5th.
Me and my friend
started screaming.
Kim Moettner taped it for me.
Everyone in my biology
class knew about it,
and I played the tape in my
Health class for everyone
to hear my name on the air.
-We're reading a
letter on the air
from a woman whose letter
we read on the air.
-Well, yeah.
We kind of--
-Kind of a bookend.
-Every six weeks, we'll
read her new letter
when she gets excited
about this one.
Then we'll read the next one.
Well, I think
that's all from us.
Bye, then.
We've got things to do.
[Robots singing]
-I'm much cleaner
than you are, Frank!
I've already removed
all my vile flesh
and now I'm removing that
dark stain from my soul!
-That's nothing, Clay.
I'm all the way down
to original sin!
-Oh yeah?
Well, I'm-- What
are you looking at?
Haven't you ever
seen two men practice
a little personal hygiene?
Hmm?
You got a problem with that?
I'll put and end to this little
naughty voyeurism right now.
-Now I'm totally clean, Clay.
Clay?
[Theme music playing]